cloutonline.com 2012-06-13

# PRIVACY POLICY – CLOUT MAGAZINE

## PRIVACY POLICY

**STATEMENT**  
Since your privacy is of the utmost importance to us, we have provided this Statement about privacy and information usage by CloutOnline.com. Any information gathered by CloutOnline.com will be kept strictly confidential and will only be used or shared in ways for which you have specifically consented. CloutOnline.com will not sell, rent or trade your personal information to any third party. We will take special care to protect the privacy and security of your information. By visiting CloutOnline.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Statement.

**YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IS PROTECTED** All personal information and transaction details you provide on CloutOnline.com’s Online Store, from your e-mail address to credit card number, is protected by 128 bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption. All payments (credit, debit, bank transfers, e-checks) are processed through PayPal, so we never see your credit card information or bank account number. When shopping online, on CloutOnline.com or elsewhere, we’d like to offer you these tips on shopping securely: Check if the web address on the page that asks for your personal information and credit card information begins with “https:” instead of “http:”. You can tell a web site uses security software if your browser displays the icon of a locked padlock at the bottom of the screen (Netscape Navigator™; – versions 4.0 and higher); if you see the icon of an unbroken key at the bottom of the screen (earlier versions of Netscape Navigator™); or if you see the icon of a lock on the status bar (Microsoft Internet Explorer®).

**HOW CLOUTONLINE.COM USES INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE**  
CloutOnline.com collects and uses your personal information to respond to your requests for information, products and services. Unless we have your express consent, your personal information will only be used or shared to fulfill your request. CloutOnline.com collects personal information when you:

Pay for products from CloutOnline.com with PayPal, which you will then be required by PayPal to provide your full name, full address, phone number, e-mail address, and if paying with a credit card, your credit card number, your credit card expiration date, and your credit card verification number, to complete your purchase. PayPal does not share your credit card information or phone number with us. From time to time we may send you announcements regarding CloutOnline.com’s updates, new arrivals and special offers through e-mail to the e-mail addresses that we have collected from PayPal. If you would not like to receive such announcements, please e-mail info@cloutonline.com.

Contact CloutOnline.com with a question or suggestion in which we collect your name, e-mail address and any comments you have. We primarily use this information to respond to and/or resolve your question or concern, but from time to time we may send you announcements regarding CloutOnline.com’s updates, new arrivals and special offers through e-mail to the e-mail addresses that we have collected from the above methods. If you would not like to receive such announcements, please e-mail info@cloutonline.com.

**HOW CLOUTONLINE.COM USES INFORMATION THAT IS AUTOMATICALLY PROVIDED**  
When you visit CloutOnline.com, like many other Web sites, we collect and analyze the information that is automatically provided such as your Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform, and what parts of our site you visit.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on CloutOnline.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to CloutOnline. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES**  
If there are changes or additions to this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we collect online or offline, how we use it and what choices you have. Regardless of any changes we make to our Privacy Policy, we will only use your personal information in accordance with the version of the Privacy Policy in place at the time you provided your information, unless you later give your express consent for us to do otherwise.

**TERMS OF USE**  
By using CloutOnline.com, you consent to the collection and use of your information by CloutOnline.com within the policies stated above. If you have any questions or concerns, please e-mail us at info@cloutonline.com.

*Last updated on May 22, 2009.
